dropapk.to 2019-08-29

# Drop APK - Easy way to share your files

This Privacy Policy together with DropAPK.To Terms and Conditions, and other conditions (Abuse Policy, DMCA) of use which are part of DropAPK.To regulates your use of the DropAPK.To website (https://DropAPK.To) and are collectively referred to as the «Agreement».

This document is a binding integral part of the contract for our users. DropAPK.To is bound to keep this integral part of the contract legally effective regarding all upload and download activities of all customers. Exceptions are applicable only if explicitly mentioned in this document or in communications. DropAPK.To may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

The following Privacy Policy relates to our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of DropAPK.To (the «Site») This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site.

When a password is used to help protect your account and/or personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer be sure to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from other users. You are solely responsible for the safeguarding of your password.

### Information

In the course of using DropAPK.To, you may provide us with personal information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (based solely on the information you provided in your account). Personal Information that we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, location, billing information (only if applicable and does not include credit card information), email address and postal addresses (if applicable). Personal Information may also include information you supply to us concerning your preferences and interests expressed in the course of use of our Site.

For your safety and protection, your payment information is not stored on our servers. Our payment providers keep this information encrypted and secure on your behalf according to their applicable policies.

### Use

DropAPK.To uses IP addresses to measure usage, analyze trends and administer the website. We also use information we obtain by technical means for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of DropAPK.To and our services, for DropAPK.To technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality, effectiveness, user-friendliness and to better service your needs and requests.

The email address you provide to the Site will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to the service requested.

We will not rent, sell or share your e-mail or information with third parties with the exception of third party companies we may contract to facilitate our services, including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management processing, etc.

Content/Data uploaded to DropAPK.To is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

DropAPK.To may use cookies to store the preferences of users. You may reject or delete the cookie. Cookies can also be used to help DropAPK.To enhance your experience on our website.

### Disclosure Of Information

DropAPK.To cooperates with governments and law enforcement agencies/officials as well as private parties to enforce and complies with laws and regulations. As such, we shall disclose any information to a government, law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole and unfettered discretion, believe is necessary or appropriate in response to claims and legal processes (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of DropAPK.To or a third party if applicable and to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider or can pose a risk to be illegal, inappropriate or legally actionable.

Please note that we may disclose your personal information or any other information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to conform with applicable laws and/or comply with a legal process served on us.

### General

DropAPK.To uses its best efforts in safeguarding information and uses reasonable measures designed to protect said information from unauthorized access.

DropAPK.To employs state of the art encryption technology and makes its best effort in order to ensure your complete privacy and security during the use of its services. All traffic, both incoming and outgoing is 100% encrypted using the latest technological solutions.

DropAPK.To is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third-party websites and companies and shall not be held responsible for their actions.

DropAPK.To is not responsible if you disclose personal information online that is accessible to the public. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or for further information, please contact us at info@DropAPK.To
